Contact

ianrichardbunn@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ianbunn (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Node.js

Full-Stack Development
Amazon Web Services (AWS)

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual) Spanish (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

- Modern Web Development with SASS, Gulp, NPM & Web Work-flows
- Lean Six Sigma Foundations Agile at Work: Planning with Agile User Stories
- Project Management Foundations: Small Projects
- Business Analysis Foundations
- Agile at Work: Planning with Agile User Stories
- More on LinkedIn...

Ian Bunn

Proper preparation prevents poor performance. Full-stack Developer & DevOps. Blockchain & cryptocurrency advocate.

Austin, Texas

Summary

Full-Stack Developer passionate about software that provides positive value to our community. Currently employed as DevOps Engineer and Internal Development, which entails making changes to and managing legacy software. I'm fluent in CSS, JS, SQL, and node.js. Previous experience includes, but not limited to: following agile methodology in software development and Project Management Professional standards to maintain control of project constraints. Self-starter and entrepreneurial attitude that enables me to clear obstacles. Strong supporter of blockchain and cryptocurrencies that provide solutions to socio-economic problems. Received BBA in Finance from Our Lady of the Lake University and Full-stack Developer Certification from University of Texas at Austin.

Experience

TCG Group Holdings, LLP.
IT Internal Development and DevOps
August 2013 - Present

Austin, Texas Area

Integration of IT solutions and implementation of internal procedures to streamline operations. With addition to development operations and AWS resource management, deploying new projects and maintaining existing software solutions.

San Diego Independent School District High School Social Studies Teacher January 2010 - August 2013 (3 years 8 months) San Diego, TX

Responsible for the following subjects: World Geography, Economics, US History and Government. Assisted in softball coaching duties leading the team to Regional rounds.

The RK Group

Personal Assistant

March 2009 - March 2010 (1 year 1 month)

San Antonio, Texas Area

Personal assistant to Chairman Emeritus and Public Relations Director, Rosemary Kowalski.

Citi

Personal Banker

July 2008 - September 2009 (1 year 3 months)

San Antonio, Texas Area

Personal banking financial services and financial product sales.

Avenida Guadalupe Association Marketing Assistant May 2008 - October 2008 (6 months)

San Antonio, Texas Area

Assisted with marketing duties and helped plan the annual 16 de Septiembre parade.

Education

The University of Texas at Austin

Full-Stack Development Certification · (2018 - 2019)

Free Code Camp

Full Stack Web Development, Computer Software Engineering · (2016 - 2017)

Our Lady of the Lake University

Bachelor's degree, Accounting and Finance · (2005 - 2008)